Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Chefs
  - Schmebeck, Daryl, undated (Box 41, Folder 134)
  - Schenk, John, 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 135)
  - Schepici, Larry, 2004-2010 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Scherber, Amy, 1992-1997 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Scherner, Bob, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Schiaffino, Pedro Miguel, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Schiavone, Peter, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Schiavone, Toto, 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Schickler, Sue, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Schifano, Salvatore, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Schillinger, Jean-Yves, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Schlesinger, Chris, 1985-1996 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Schloss, Kenneth, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Schlow, Michael, 1995-1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Schluntz, Karen, 1987-1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Schmid, Carl Otto, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Schmidt, Christian, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Schmidt, Jimmy, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Schmidt, Mark, 2004-2006 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Schmidt, Stephen, 1987-1991 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Schmit, Philippe, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Schnaars, Guy, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Schneider, Sally, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Schnider, Roland, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Schenegger, Theo, 1993-2000 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Schoenegger, Theo, 1993-2000 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Schommer, Chuck, 1992-1997 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Schlotte, Martin, 1998-2004 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Schlotts, Andrew, 2002-2006 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Schreiber, Cory, 1995-2003 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Schroeder, Carl, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Schroeder, Lisa, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Schulson, Michael, 1998-2002 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Schultz, Christian, 1989-2005 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Schumacher, John, 1988-1995 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Schultz, Bill, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Schutz, Pierre, 1994-2002 (Box 42, Folder 33a)
  - Schwartz, Leonard, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 33b)
  - Schwartz, Michael, 1995-2002 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Schwartz, Warren, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Schweder, Helmut, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Scheitzer, Hans, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Sciandi, Agostino, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Scicolone, Michele, 1997-2006 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Scism, Jennifer, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Scosos, Roxsand, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Scothorn, Chad, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Scott, Sarah, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Scott, Tim, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Scott, Pietro, 1995-2000 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Scotto, John, undated (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Scotto, Vincent, 1993-2002 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Scully, Matthew, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Sear, Kerry, 1991-1999 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Secchi, Stephano, 1998-2004 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Secci, Enzo, undated (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Sedlar, John, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Seeber, Matthew, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Seeger, Guenter, 1996-1999 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Segal, Mindy, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Segawa-Gonzales, Mako, undated (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Segel, Mark, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Seger, Louis, 1992-2000 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Sehnert, Thom and Jane, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Seidel, Alex, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Seidman, Paul, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Sein, Gregoire, undated (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Selby, Matt, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Seleno, Bill, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Sell, Chris, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Selman, Farrin, 1993-1997 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Selvaggio, Piero, 1988-1997 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - Selvarajah, Carol, 1992-1997 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Sena, Stefano, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Sendel, Jean, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Senne, Renee, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Sepe, Christopher, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - SerendipiTea, undated (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - Serrano, Carmen and Luis, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - Serrano, Julian, 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - Serpao, Scott, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - Settepani, Biago, undated (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - Sewall, Jeremy, undated (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - Shaeffer, Jason, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - Shafer, Michael S., undated (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - Shaffer, Bev, undated (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - Shani, Eyal, undated (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - Shannon James P. (Jamie), 1992-2001 (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - Shariat, Anoosh, undated (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - Sharon, Mika, undated (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - Sharp, Ken, undated (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - Share Our Strengh, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - Shea, Becky, undated (Box 42, Folder 88)
  - Shea, Chris, undated (Box 42, Folder 89)
  - Shea, David, 2000-2005 (Box 42, Folder 90)
  - Sheehan, Lynn, 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 91)
  - Sheehan, Terry, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 92)
  - Sheely, John, 1998-2003 (Box 42, Folder 93)
  - Sheerin, Patrick, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 94)
  - Shelby, Matt, undated (Box 42, Folder 95)
  - Shelley, Darrin, 2003-2008 (Box 42, Folder 96)
  - Shelton, Craig, 1992-2000 (Box 42, Folder 97)
  - Shepard, Adam, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 98)
  - Sherman, Ben, undated (Box 42, Folder 99)
  - Sherman, Bruce, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 100)
  - Sheve, Lindsay, undated (Box 42, Folder 101)
  - Shikami, Kevin, 1988-2003 (Box 42, Folder 102)
  - Shilling, Joseph, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 103)
  - Shima, Hiroshi, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 104)
  - Shimbo, Hiroko, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 105)
  - Shinagawa, Dean, 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 106)
  - Shinu, Barbara, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 107)
  - Shirley, Norma, 1987-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Shively, Jeffery, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Shoup, Allen, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Shrader, Michael, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Shulman, Martha Rose, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Shulte, Anton, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Sibley, Barbara and Magritte Malfy, 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Sicolo, Todd, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Siddu, Patrizio, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Sieber, Dawn, 1995-1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Sieber, Wendy, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Siegel, Adam, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Siegel, Ron, 1996-2002 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Siegel, Ted, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Sierra Grill, 1992-1996 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Signori, Scott, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Sikhattana, John, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Sikka, Gary (Mint), 2006 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Silberman, Alan (Custard Beach), undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Silsdorf, William, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Silva, Albino, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Silva, Mark, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Silverberg, Marc, undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Silverman, Andrew, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Silverman, Dan, undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Silverman, Matthew, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Silvers, Josh, undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Silverton, Nancy, 1999-2002 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Simeon, Eric, undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Simmons, Charles, undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Simmons, Stephen, undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Simon, Kerry, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Simone, Joe, undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Sinclair, Gordon, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Sinclair, Mark, undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Sindaco, Tony, undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Sindoni, Vittorio & Family, undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Sing Gill, Santhok, Aug. 1995; various (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Singer, Steven, undated (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Singh, Sonan, undated (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Sinskey, Robert, undated (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Sippel, Kurt, undated (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Siu, Russel, undated (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Skawinski, Lee, undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Skeen, Ryan, undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Skelley, Sean, undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Skokan, Eric, undated (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Slack, Mark, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Slate, Geoffrey, undated (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Slatkin, David, undated (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Slawson, Mark, undated (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Sloane, David, undated (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Slossberg, Todd, undated (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Small, Rick, undated (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Smith and Wollensky, undated (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Smith, Ben, undated (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Smith, Bill, undated (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Smith, Chip, undated (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Smith, Dayn R., undated (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Smith, Glenn, undated (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Smith, Holly, undated (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Smith, Jason, undated (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Smith, Jeff, undated (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Smith, Michael, undated (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Smith, Michael and Debbie Gold, undated (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Smith, Mike, undated (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Smith, Peter, undated (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Smith, Quint, undated (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Smith, Richard, undated (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - Smith, Stephen, undated (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Sterling, undated (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - Sneed, Jimmy, undated (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - Snow, Kimberly, undated (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - Sobel, Adam, undated (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - Sodamin, Rudi, undated (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - Soisson, Neika, undated (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - Sola, John, undated (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - Solinas, Raffaele, undated (Box 43, Folder 78)
  - Solliard, Claude, undated (Box 43, Folder 79)
  - Solomon, Allison, undated (Box 43, Folder 80)
  - Solomon, Charles, undated (Box 43, Folder 81)
  - Solomon, Jim, undated (Box 43, Folder 82)
  - Solomonov, Michael, undated (Box 43, Folder 83)
  - Solther, Andre, undated (Box 43, Folder 84)
  - Somerstein, Joel, undated (Box 43, Folder 85)
  - Sone, Hiro, undated (Box 43, Folder 86)
  - Sonnier, Greg & Mary, undated (Box 43, Folder 87)
  - Sontheimer, Carl, undated (Box 43, Folder 88)
  - Sonveau, Nicolas, undated (Box 43, Folder 89)
  - Sootoo, David, undated (Box 43, Folder 90)
  - Sorel, Christophe, undated (Box 43, Folder 91)
  - Sorenson, Christian, undated (Box 43, Folder 92)
  - Sorenson, Goose, undated (Box 43, Folder 93)
  - Sorenson, John Bach, undated (Box 43, Folder 94)
  - Sorenson, Lasse, undated (Box 43, Folder 95)
  - Soriano, Denis, undated (Box 43, Folder 96)
  - Sortun, Ana, undated (Box 43, Folder 97)
  - Sotelino, Gabino, undated (Box 43, Folder 98)
  - Sougan, Tim, undated (Box 43, Folder 99)
  - Soule, Henri, undated (Box 43, Folder 100)
  - Soury, Alan, undated (Box 43, Folder 101)
  - Spagnolo, Tosario, undated (Box 43, Folder 102)
  - Spagenthal, Mark, undated (Box 43, Folder 103)
  - Sparks, Katy, undated (Box 43, Folder 104)
  - Speers, Dana, undated (Box 43, Folder 105)
  - Speidel, Champe, undated (Box 43, Folder 106)
  - Spicer, Susan, undated (Box 43, Folder 107)
  - Spilecki, Brian, undated (Box 43, Folder 108)
  - Spiliadis, Costas, undated (Box 43, Folder 109)
  - Spitz, William, undated (Box 43, Folder 110)
  - Spitzer, Mark, undated (Box 43, Folder 111)
  - Splichal, Joachim, undated (Box 43, Folder 112)
  - Spost, Louis, undated (Box 43, Folder 113)
  - Spiro, Scarmine, undated (Box 43, Folder 114)
  - Spyropoulos, Peter, undated (Box 43, Folder 115)
  - Stachowski, Jamie, undated (Box 43, Folder 116)
  - Stafford, Craig, undated (Box 43, Folder 117)
  - Stage, Daniel, undated (Box 43, Folder 118)
  - Stage, John, undated (Box 43, Folder 119)
  - Stahler, Michael, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Staib, Walter, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Stair, Cheryl, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Stair, Pam, undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Stamenor, Cal, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Stannard, Russel, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Stanton, Debra, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Stapelman, Eric, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Stapelton, Brian, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Stark, Ivy, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Stark, Mark, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Starr Restaurant Organization, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Starr, Stephen, undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Starwalt, Richard, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - State, John, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Staub, Rusty, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Stebner, Michael, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Steelman, Brad, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Steffenelli, Enzo, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Stegner, Sarah, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Sterling, Robert, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Stein, Judith, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Stein, Rick, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Stein, Stu, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Steinberg, Owen, undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Stindler, Paul, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - St. Joseph's Day, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - St. Hilaire, Jonathan, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Stellio, Nick, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Stephens, Warren, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Stephenson, Craig, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Stephenson, Gavin, undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Stephenson, Gregorio, undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Stephenson, Tim, undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Steppe, Charles and Maureen Brown, undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Sterling, Willard, undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Stern, Bonnie, undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Stern, Daniel, undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Sternweiler, Allen, undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Stevens, Brad, undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Steward, Natalie, undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Stewart-Godon, Faith, undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Stichter, Drew, undated (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Stitt, Frank, undated (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Stockhammer, Franz, undated (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Stone, Edward, undated (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Stone, Jeffrey, undated (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Stone, Larry, undated (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Stowell, Ethan, undated (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Strandberg, Ulf Anders, undated (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Stratta, Alessandro, undated (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Strausman, Mark, undated (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Strehl, Gary, undated (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Streng, Goran, undated (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Strout, Michel, undated (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Studley, George and Helen, undated (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Sturkey, Paul, undated (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Suarez, David, undated (Box 44, Folder 58a)
  - Subra, Chuck, undated (Box 44, Folder 58b)
  - Suguira, Katsuo, undated (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Sugiyama, Nashiko, undated (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Suhanosky, Ron, undated (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Suhner, Max, undated (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Suatycky, Robert, undated (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Sullivvan, Brian, undated (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Sullivan, Mark, undated (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Sullivan, Michael, undated (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Summers, Marc, undated (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Sung, Luke, undated (Box 44, Folder 68a)
  - Sunshine Cuisine, undated (Box 44, Folder 68b)
  - Sushi Samba, undated (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Susi, Anthony, undated (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Suley, John, undated (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Sundstrom, Jonathan, undated (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Susser, Alan, undated (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Sutton, Andrew, undated (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Svalesen, Christian, undated (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Svenson, Johan, undated (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Swahn, Hakan, undated (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Sweet Grass Dairy, undated (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Swersky, Andrew, undated (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Swift, Jay, undated (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Swingle-Kido Catering, undated (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Swinney, Dan, undated (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Syman, Michel, undated (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Szathmary, Louis I., undated (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Szekretar, Scott, undated (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Szmania, Ludger, undated (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - Szurdak, Jean Claude, undated (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Taboda, John, undated (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - Tachibe, Shigefumi, undated (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Tacquet, Jean-Francois, undated (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Taournet, undated (Box 44, Folder 91)
  - Taillevent, undated (Box 44, Folder 92)
  - Takanashi, Testsuro, undated (Box 44, Folder 93)
  - Takase, Eiji, undated (Box 44, Folder 94)
  - Takashi, Michi, undated (Box 44, Folder 95)
  - Tamayo, James, undated (Box 44, Folder 96)
  - Tammero, Anthony, undated (Box 44, Folder 97)
  - Tamura, Angela, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Tan, Patrick, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Tanaka, Eric, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Tanaka, Eric, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Tanaka, Makoto, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Tang, Tommy, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tanner, Bruce, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Tarbell, Mark, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Tardi, Alan, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - undated (Box 45, Folder data_value_missing_221382f5ef0c134022ba54504a0042c0)
  - Tarrin, David, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Tasca Lanza, Anna, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Tassa, Salvatore, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Taub, Steven, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Taubin, Elaine, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Taus, Michael, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Tavern on the Green, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Taylor, Curt, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, Kevin, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Taxiera, Marc, undated (Box 45, Folder 17a)
  - Teichman, Dave, undated (Box 45, Folder 17b)
  - Telepan, Bill, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - TV Food Network, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Tellez, Guillermo, undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Tello, Alonzo, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Tenner, Jeffrey, undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Tentation Catering, undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Terano, Koji, undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Terava, Pekka, undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Terillo, Maryann, undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Terje, Staffan, undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Ternes, Francois, undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Terry, Elizabeth, undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Terzi, Stefano, undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Tesar, John, undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Tessler, Jonathan, undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Testa, Maryjo, undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Teulade, Jean Claude, undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Thanksgiving Farm, undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Thiebeult, Jacques, undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Thomas, Bob, undated (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Thomas, Craig, undated (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Thomas, Dave (Wendy's), undated (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Thomas, David, undated (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Thomas, Guillermo (Willie), undated (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Thomas, Roger, undated (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Thompson, Brad, undated (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Thompson, Bradley, undated (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Thompson, David, undated (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Thompson, Gerard, undated (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Thompson, Justin, undated (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Thompson, Liz, undated (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Thompson, Richard and Peggy, undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Thompson, Troy, undated (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Thomson, Michael, undated (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Thorburn, Mary Louise, undated (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Thorne, John, undated (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Thurber, Allyson, undated (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Thymes Two, undated (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Ticarro, Christian, undated (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Ticarro, Christophe, undated (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Tillinghast, Bruce and Pat, undated (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Timmins, Peter, undated (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Timmins, Peter, undated (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Tingle, Ralph, undated (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - Tio, Celina, undated (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - Tischler, Nicholas, undated (Box 45, Folder 62)
  - Titland, Russel, undated (Box 45, Folder 63)
  - Tivy, Matthew, undated (Box 45, Folder 64)
  - Todd, Christopher, undated (Box 45, Folder 65)
  - Toedter, Uwe, undated (Box 45, Folder 66)
  - Toler, John A., undated (Box 45, Folder 67)
  - Tong, Michael, undated (Box 45, Folder 68)
  - Tonon, Rina, undated (Box 45, Folder 69)
  - Topple, Steve, undated (Box 45, Folder 70)
  - Torres, Jacques, undated (Box 45, Folder 71)
  - Torres, Jorge, undated (Box 45, Folder 72)
  - Torres, Sue, undated (Box 45, Folder 73)
  - Torrz, Victor Maglioli, undated (Box 45, Folder 74)
  - Tostrup, Jason, undated (Box 45, Folder 75)
  - Toufayan, Arthur, undated (Box 45, Folder 76)
  - Tougne, Dominique, undated (Box 45, Folder 77)
  - Tour de Forks, undated (Box 45, Folder 78)
  - Tourondel, Laurent, undated (Box 45, Folder 79)
  - Toury, Christophe, undated (Box 45, Folder 80)
  - Tovar, Cedric, undated (Box 45, Folder 81)
  - Tower, Jeremiah, undated (Box 45, Folder 82)
  - Travocchi, Fabio, undated (Box 45, Folder 83)
  - Tracey, James, undated (Box 45, Folder 84)
  - Tracht, Suzanne, undated (Box 45, Folder 85)
  - Trainor, Bob, undated (Box 45, Folder 86)
  - Trama, Joe, undated (Box 45, Folder 87)
  - Trama, Pat, undated (Box 45, Folder 88)
  - Tramanto, Rick, undated (Box 45, Folder 89)
  - Tran, Viet, undated (Box 45, Folder 90)
  - Traslavina, Riccardo, undated (Box 45, Folder 91)
  - Traunfeld, Jerry, undated (Box 45, Folder 92)
  - Travi, Jason, undated (Box 45, Folder 93)
  - Trboyevic, Jovan, undated (Box 45, Folder 94)
  - Trevino, Roberto, undated (Box 45, Folder 95)
  - Treadwell, Evan, undated (Box 45, Folder 96)
  - Trinidad, Anthony, undated (Box 45, Folder 97)
  - Trigg, Bobby, undated (Box 45, Folder 98)
  - Trobo, Pablo, undated (Box 45, Folder 99)
  - Trocca, Fernando, undated (Box 45, Folder 100)
  - Troisgros, Claude, undated (Box 45, Folder 101)
  - Troisgros, Pierre, undated (Box 45, Folder 102)
  - Treux, Joseph, undated (Box 45, Folder 103)
  - Trojahn, Stephen, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Trosch, Phillipe, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Trotters, Charlie, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Trova, Enrico, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Truscio, Jason, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Tsai, Ming, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Tse, Albert, undated (Box 46, Folder 8a)
  - Tsuchida, Ritsuo, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 8b)
  - Tunks, Jeff, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Turner, Andrew, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Turner, John, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Tusk, Michael, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Tutino, Charles, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Twyman, Steven, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Tyler, Vince, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Tzolis, Steve, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Tzul, Andres, undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Ubaldi, Jack, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Ubert, Scott, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Uddo, Michael, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Uehlein, Scott, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Ulak, Jason, undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Ulbrich, Charles, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Umami, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Unique Restaurant Concepts, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Unterholzner, Karl, undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Upchurch, Matt, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Upshur, Greg, undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Upstairs on the Square, undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Urato, Mike, undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Urban, Sonia, undated (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Urena, Alex, undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Urguiles, Mario, undated (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Utagawa, Daisuke, undated (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Uyemura, Robert S., undated (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Uygur, David, undated (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Vandaele, Bart, undated (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Vaccarello, Patrick, undated (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Vaccaro, Thomas, undated (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Valenti, Duilio, undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Valenti, Tom, undated (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Valentin, Yvan, undated (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Valentine, William, undated (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Valiani, Marc, undated (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Valles, Jordi, undated (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Vallone, Joey, undated (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Vallone, TOny, undated (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Van Aken, Norman, undated (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Van Bourgondien, Andrew, undated (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Van Cleave, Jill, undated (Box 46, Folder 50)